mikeyounglaw.com 2019-02-14

# Privacy Policy - Dallas Business Lawyer

This is the privacy policy for the website of Internet Lawyer Mike Young’s Law Office of Michael E. Young PLLC, a Texas professional limited liability company.

## Law Firm Contact Information

The law firm’s postal address is:

5960 West Parker Road  
Suite 278 PMB 421  
Plano, Texas 75093 USA

The firm can be reached via e-mail by using our [contact form](https://mikeyounglaw.com/internet-lawyer/contact-us/) or by telephone at 214-546-4247.

## Information Collected

[](https://mikeyounglaw.com/website-legal-protection/)For each visitor to this website, the Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding your name, domain name(s) or e-mail address(es). It may identify your Internet Protocol (IP) address.

The law firm collects the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to the blog, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with the business via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages website visitors access or visit, information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey information and/or site registrations.The information collected is used to improve the content of this website.

With respect to cookies: this website sets cookies to customize the welcome greeting you receive as a visitor.

If you use social media buttons on the Website (e.g. the Facebook “Like”, a Google+ “share”, or a Twitter “tweet” button), you will be providing certain information about yourself with the social media sites. For example, this shared information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address and other information about you based upon the content you marked or shared using the social media button, as well as any comments you made about the content when using social media.

## Emails and Mailings

If you do not want to receive e-mail from [Internet Lawyer Young](https://mikeyounglaw.com/category/internet-lawyer-2/) or the law firm in the future, please let us know by sending an e-mail using the contact form on this website or send your request by postal mail to the address listed above.

If you supply our Internet law firm with your postal address online, you may receive periodic mailings with information on new products and services or upcoming events.

If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling the phone number listed above. Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list.

## Privacy Policy Changes

From time to time, we may use visitor information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in this privacy notice. If information practices change at some time in the future, our business will post the policy changes to this website to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at this [Internet law firm](https://mikeyounglaw.com/category/internet-lawyer-2/internet-law-business-2/) website periodically.

## Other Issues

Website visitors may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us through the Internet lawyer contact form linked to above.

Upon request, we provide site visitors with access to a description of information we maintain about them. Website visitors can access this information by writing to the Internet law firm at the above address.

If you feel that this [Internet lawyer](https://mikeyounglaw.com/internet-lawyer-business-choices/) site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above address or phone number.

## California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident and our customer, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83 permits you to request certain information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To request this information, please send an email using this website’s [contact form](https://mikeyounglaw.com/contact-us/) or write us at the following address:

Law Office of Michael E. Young PLLC

5960 W. Parker Rd., Ste. 278 PMB 421

Plano, Texas 75093

United States

## European Union Privacy Rights

If you reside in the European Union, you may have certain privacy rights under Regulation (EU) 2016/679, the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), to the extent the GDPR does not conflict with the laws of Texas and United States. Even if we do not have a legal obligation to do so, we may respond to your requests made per the GDPR. However, voluntary responses are not a waiver of our legal rights and obligations under the laws of Texas and United States or the arbitration provisions found within our website’s [Terms of Use](https://mikeyounglaw.com/internet-attorney-terms-use/).

### Small Or Medium-Sized Enterprise Status

We are a small or medium-sized enterprise (“SME”). This means that because of the size of our business, to the extent (if any) the GDPR governs our relationship with you, some of GDPR’s obligations do not apply because we are an SME.

### How To Make A Request

To make a GDPR request, please send an email using our website’s [contact form](https://mikeyounglaw.com/contact-us/) or write us at the following address:

Law Office of Michael E. Young PLLC

5960 W. Parker Rd., Ste. 278 PMB 421

Plano, Texas 75093

United States

We will respond within thirty (30) days of receipt of your request.

### Requests To Access Personal Data

If we grant your request to access personal data, we will: (1) confirm whether or not we are processing your personal data; (2) provide you with a copy of any of your personal data that we possess; and (3) provide you with information about how we process such data (e.g. purposes, categories, recipients, etc.).

### Requests To Delete Data

If you request that we delete your personal data that we possess, we will do so unless: (1) the data is needed to exercise the right of freedom of expression; (2) we have a legal obligation to keep the data; (3) we must keep the data for reasons of public interest; or (4) the data has been processed so that it is anonymized.

Any personal data we processed unlawfully will be deleted. If you were a minor when we collected the personal data, we will delete the data upon request.

If we believe any third parties have acquired your personal data through us, we will take reasonable steps to inform them that you have requested erasure of such data.

### Objections To Processing Of Personal Data

If your request is an objection to the processing of your personal data for directing marketing purposes, we will cease using your data for such purposes.

As a general rule, we will comply with objections to processing personal data except: (1) where it is not technically or commercially feasible to do so; or (2) we have a legal obligation that overrides your individual rights and freedoms.

### Portability Requests

If we collected personal data from you because of a contract between us or based on your consent, and we processed that data by automated means (in structured machine-readable format), you can request that data be transmitted by us to another company or organization.

We will provide such data to the recipient third party in a commonly used open format electronic file (e.g. CSV, JSON, XML, etc.).

### Denied Requests

If we reject your request, we will provide you with the reason(s) for doing so. You may then choose to file a complaint with the Data Protection Authority and request a judicial remedy to the extent such a request is not in conflict with the laws of laws of Texas and United States or the arbitration provisions of our website’s Terms and Conditions of Use).

### Processing Fees

As a general rule, there is no fee for processing your GDPR request. However, we reserve the right to refuse your request or charge a reasonable fee for processing it if the request is manifestly unfounded or excessive. For example, it would be excessive to make a repetitive second request to access your personal data one month after we provided you with the data from a prior request.

## When This Website Privacy Policy Was Last Modified

This [website privacy policy](https://mikeyounglaw.com/website-privacy-policy-faqs/) was last updated on May 25, 2018.
